You Red Welby?
你是Red Welby?
Yes, ma'am. How may I help you?
是的，需要什么帮助？
I heard there's three billboards out on Drinkwater Road...
我听说引水路边上有三个广告牌
you're in charge of renting them out, that right?
你是负责租赁的，对吧？
I didn't know we had any billboards out on Drinkwater...
我没听说我们在饮水路上有什么广告牌
- Where is Drinkwater Road? - there's a Road out past the Sizemore got put in.
饮水路在哪儿？ 那条穿过Sizemore的路
Turn-off nobody uses since the highway,
自从有了高速，没人在走那条道了
You are right.
你说的对
Got three billboards out there. Nobody's put nothing up out there since... 1986.
查到了，确实有三个广告牌，不过从1986年起就每人在挂广告了
That was 'Huggies'.
这倒不稀奇哈
How much to rent out all three of 'em the year?
这三个一年租金多少钱？
A year?
一整年？
You wanna pay for three billboards on a road no-one goes down
你想花钱租一条没人走的道上的广告牌
unless they got lost or they're retards, for a year?
出非有人走丢了才区那条路，你要租下一整年？
Quick, ain't ya, Welby?
麻利点，Welby
Well...
好吧
since what I say goes these days down at the Ebbing Advertising Desk,
鉴于我在Ebbing广告公司这些年的工龄
I'm gonna strike you a real good deal on those billboards,
我会给你报一个好价格
now, what was it you said your name was, Mrs...?
请问，怎么称呼您？
What's the law on what ya can and cannot say on a billboard?
广告牌上能写什么不能写什么，你们有规定吗？
I assume it's ya can't say nothing defamatory,
我想你不能在上面挂诽谤言论
and ya can't say, 'Fuck' 'Piss' or 'Cunt'. That right?
也不能说『操』『逼』之类的脏话，对吧？
Or...
还有
Anus.
菊花
Well I think I'll be alright then.
我想这不是问题
Here's five thousand for the first month. I assume that'll cover it.
这是第一个月的5000块，绰绰有余了吧
Here's what the billboards oughta say.
这是我要挂在广告牌上的
Why don't ya draw up a little contract betwixt us while you're at it,
为啥不草拟一份合同
make sure nobody rents them billboards out from under me?
确保没人从我名下抢走这些广告牌
I guess you're Angela Hayes' mother.
我猜你是Angela Hayes的妈妈
That's right, I'm Angela Hayes' mother.
对，我就是Angela Hayes的母亲
Name's Mildred.
名字是Mildred.
How long before you've got 'em put up?
你们把广告挂上去要花多久？
Oh, shall we say by...
嗯，我们能在…
Easter Sunday?
复活节的周日搞定？
That'd be perfect.
那太好了
- Hey! What the hell's this?! - Que?
嘿！这他妈是什么？ Que?
- “How come Chief Willoughby?” what?- What?
- “Willoughby警官怎么了？”什么？- 什么？
- Yeah!- Huh!
- 是的！- 哼！
How come what?
怎么了？
What?!
什么？！
Listen, I better start getting some straight answers outta you
听着，你最好直截了当的告诉我
you Put that down.
你把它放下。
What the Hell is this?
这到底是什么？
Hey you?
嘿，是你？
What the fuck is this?
这他妈的是什么？
- What the fuck is what?- This! This!
- 他妈的是什么？- 这个！这个！
- Advertising, I guess.- Advertising what?
- 广告，我猜。- 广告什么？
Something obscure?
一些讽刺的东西？
I'll say! Yeah!
我就说！是啊！
Don't I know your face from some place?
我是不是在哪儿见过你的脸？
- I dunno, do ya?- Yeah.
- 我不知道，是吗？- 是的。
Yeah, I do.
是的。
I could arrest you rightnow, if I wanted to.
如果我想的话，我现在可以逮捕你。
- For what?- For... emptying out your bucket there. It's against the...
- 凭什么？- 随地吐痰。这违反了...
being bad against the environment laws.
违反环境保护法。
Before you do that,
在你做之前，
Officer Dixon,
Dixon警官 ,
How about you go have yourself a look at that first billboard over there,
你怎么去看看那边的第一张广告牌，
and then we can have ourself a conversation about the motherfucking environment.
然后我们可以谈谈这个他妈的环境保护。
How about that?
怎么样？
Fuck me.
我操。
Don't...
别...
Dixon, you goddam asshole, I'm in the middle of my goddam Easter dinner...
Dixon，你这个混蛋，我她妈在吃复活节晚餐...
Sorry, kids.
抱歉，孩子们。
I know, Chief, and I'm sorry for calling ya at home and all, but uh,
我知道，长官，很抱歉打电话给你，但是，
I think we've got kind of a problem...
我想我们遇到了一些问题
No. No. Go back.
不，不，回去。
Alright.
好了。
Sorry I'm late, Denise.
对不起，我迟到了，Denise。
Did you put up those billboards to fuck with the cops yet?
你把那些广告挂上去羞辱那些警察了吗？
They're up.
挂起来了
You go, girl! You go fuck those cops up!
好样的！去他妈的那些警察！
What the fuck do you think you're doing, Welby, buncha billboards like that,
你以为你在做什么，Welby？这样的广告牌，
you didn't think there'd be some kinda ramifications? Legally?
你不觉得会有一些法律上的争议吗？
What's the legal ramifications, Cedric?
什么是法律争议，Cedric?
You want me to explain the legal ramifications, a little punk like you?
你要我解释一下法律的争议，像你这样的朋克？
And don't call me Cedric.
别叫我 Cedric.
Ain't contravening no laws on propriety, ain't contravening no laws on any fucking thing.
不违反礼仪法律，不存在他妈的任何法律问题。
- I checked all this up.- Oh yeah, where'd you check all this up?
- 我都查过了. - 噢，你在哪儿查的？
In a...
在一本...
- book. - Which book, genius?
- 书里。 - 哪本书，天才？
Book called 'Suck my ass, it's none o' your business'.
书叫『舔我屁股』，关你屁事。
Fuck.
他妈的。
How long has this person, or persons,
这人或团伙，
rented these billboards out for?
租了多久的广告牌？
Oh, the year.
哦，一年。
And how long she actually paid for?
她付了多长时间的？
The year.
一年的。
So it's a she, isn't?
所以是的女的，对不对？
Ain't at liberty to divulge that kinda information, Chief.
长官，我无权泄露这种客户信息。
Mildred Hayes, perhaps?
Mildred Hayes，也许？
Ain't at liberty to divulge that kinda information, Chief.
长官，我无权泄露这种信息。
Do you really wanna fuck with the Ebbing Police Department, Red?
你他妈的想和Ebbing的警察部门杠上吗，Red？
Do ya?
你敢吗？
I guess.
我可不敢。
- He said what?! To your face?! - No crime has been committed here.
- 他说什么？！怼你一脸？
- 这又不违法。
C'mon Defamation of character ain't a crime?
诽谤难道不是犯罪？
It isn't defamation if she's simply asking a question.
如果她只是在提一个问题，那不是诽谤。
- What are you, an idiot? - Don't call me an idiot, Dixon.
- 你是傻逼吗？ - 别喊我傻逼。Dixon
I didn't call you an idiot. I asked if you was an idiot. It was a question.
我没有喊你傻逼。我只是在问你是不是傻逼？这是一个问题。
He got ya, Cedric!
他懂的，Cedric!
- That's it. C'mon man. Don't go fly off the handle!
- 行了，行了。
- 别他妈又把事儿玩儿脱了！
- Why in hell you keep that man on?
- He's a good man. At heart.
- 你他妈咋还留着这家伙？
- 他是一个好人。心眼不坏。
- He tortured a guy in custody, Bill. There was no...
他虐待过一个在押的犯人，Bill. 没有...
real evidence to support that.
真正的证据来支撑这件事
Take 'em down.
把广告给我撤下。
- Hah?- Take that shit down.
- 哈？ 他妈的撤了
- Take what shit down?  Hey boy.
- 他妈扯什么？  嗨，兄弟。
You think I wouldn't take you out, right here on Main Street, Red?
你以为在主街上我就不能把你抓起来，Red？
I Thought you only take out black dudes, Dixon...
我以为你只会抓黑人呢，Dixon...
That's it. No no.
这就对了。不，不。
Stop it! Don't; you ever fucking touch me, you motherfucker.
停！别;你他妈的敢碰我，操你妈。
Are you drunk?
你喝醉了吗？
Are you drunk right now?  Get up
你现在醉了吗？- 起来
nobody never goes down that road, anyways.
反正也没有人会走那条路。
Unless they got lost, or they're retards.
除非有人迷路才去那条道
Well, don't be nervous, is the main thing, and it'll go just fine.
主要是别紧张，一切都没问题
Don't look into the camera, obviously. Let's hold for this car.
不要直视相机 等这辆车过去
In three, two, one.
三，二，一。
So, Mildred Hayes, why did you put up these billboards?
所以，Mildred Hayes，你为什么挂这些广告牌？
Well, my daughter, Angela, she got abducted, and she got raped and murdered seven months ago,
我的女儿Angela，七个月前她惨遭绑架，被人强奸杀害，
on this self-same stretch o' road here,
就在这条道路上，
Whatcha watching, Momma? The stupid news?
妈在看啥呢？愚蠢的社会新闻？
It seems like the local police department is too busy goin' round torturing black folks
看来当地警察局太忙了，只有功夫残害黑人
to be bothered doing anything about solving actual crime,
在解决实际犯罪方面实在腾不出功夫
I thought these here billboards might concentrate their minds some.
我认为这些广告牌可能会让他们集中精神些。
Fuck.
他妈的。
I don't know what the police are doing, to be honest with you.
我不知道警察都在忙活啥，老实讲。
I do know my daughter's burnt body
我知道我女儿的烧伤的尸体
is lying six feet under the ground while they're eating Krispy Kremes
正躺在六尺之下，而这些警察却在吃甜甜圈
and busting eight year-olds for skateboarding in parking lots.
或者在停车场玩8岁儿童的滑板。
And Chief Willoughby, why single him out?
为什么单独拎出来Willoughby警官？
Well, he's the head of 'em, ain't he? The buck's gotta stop at somewhere.
他是领导，对吧？ 事儿总要找个头儿。
And the buck stops at Willoughby?
所以就选了Willoughby？
Yeah, the buck stops at Willoughby. Dead right it does.
是的，就是Willoughby.
You alright there, fella?
你还好吗，伙计？
Looks like we got a war on our hands.
看起来我们得有一场硬仗要打了。
Can we talk?
我们可以聊聊吗？
I'd do anything to catch the
guy who did it, Mrs. Hayes.
Hayes太太，我会尽全力去抓犯人的。
But when the DNA don't match no-one who's ever been arrested,
但是DNA和任何一个嫌疑犯都不匹配，
and when the DNA don't match any other crime nationwide,
而且DNA与全国的罪犯都不匹配
and when there wasn't a single eyewitness from the time she left your house
而且从她离开家
to the time we found her, well,
到到我们发现她尸体，全程没有目击者
right now there ain't too much more that we can do
现在我们已经尽所有可能调查了
you Could pull blood from every man and boy in this town,
你可以从这个城镇的每一个男人和男孩身上抽血，
over the age of eight.
只要超过八岁。
There's civil rights laws prevents that, Mrs. Hayes,
但公民权利法律不允许这么弄，Hayes夫人
and what if he was just passing thru town...
而如果犯人只是经过城镇的路人呢...
Pull blood from ever' man in the country, then.
那就要从全国的男人身上抽血了。
And what if he was just passing thru the country?
而如果他只是路过咱们国家呢？
If it was me,
如果是我，
I'd start up a database,
我会建立一个数据库，
every male baby what's born, stick 'em on it,
每个男婴出生起，在上面建立档案，
and as soon as they done something wrong, cross reference it
一旦他们犯了罪，都能查的到
make a hundred percent certain it was a correct match,
百分百能保证找到匹配，
then kill 'em.
然后杀了他们。
Yeah, well, there's
好吧
definitely civil rights laws prevents that.
但民权法绝对不允许这种事儿
I'm doing everything I can to track him down,
我正在尽我所能追踪犯人，
I don't think those billboards is very fair.
我认为这些广告牌是非常不公平的。
The time it's took you to get out here whining like a bitch, Willoughby,
你像个泼妇一样来找我理论的功夫，，Willoughby
some other poor girl's probably out there being butchered right now,
另外一些可怜的女孩也许现在正在惨遭杀害，
but I'm glad you've got your priorities straight, I'll say that for ya.
我很高你已经帮你弄明白什么才是优先级最高的事儿，我说完了。
There's something else, Mildred.
还有别的，Mildred。
I got cancer.
我得了癌症
- I'm dying. I know it.
- 我快死了。 我知道。
Huh?
咦？
I know it. Most everybody in town knows it.
我知道。镇里大多数人都知道。
Then you still putting up those billboard?
那你还挂这些广告牌？
Well, they wouldn't be as effective after you croak, right?
你要是挂了他们更不会负责了，对吧？
Well looky looky,
看看
if it ain't the instigator of this whole goddam affair in the first place...
这不就是整个混帐事件的煽动者吗
I didn't instigate shit, Dixon...
我没煽动，Dixon...
Playing pool against the town midget.
在和镇上的侏儒打台球啊
He's right, Red, you are playing pool against the town midget.
他是对的，Red，你正在和侏儒打球。
Well he's a cop, y'know, he's observant.
他是个警察，你知道，真是明察秋毫啊。
You know, I always disliked you, Red,
你知道，我不喜欢你，Red
ever since you was a snotty little child,
从你打小就是一个脾气暴躁的小孩，
which you still look like. A snotty little child.
现在你仍然看起来像个小屁孩。
Well that's unfortunate. I always thought you was great.
让你失望了 我一直觉得你很棒。
Even your name, 'Red Welby'.
甚至你的名字，“Red Welby”。
Even your name I disliked.
连你的名字我不喜欢。
Well... okay.
哦，那好吧。
Like you was some kind of a goddam Communist or something,
你就像一个共和党人或者类似的
- and proud of it. - No,
- 还自以为傲。- 不，
it's cos I got red hair.
这是因为我有红头发。
Do you know what they do to fagots down in Cuba, Welby?
你知道他们在古巴怎么对同性恋吗，Welby?
Wow, that's left-field...
哇，真是长见识…
No, what do they do to fagots down in Cuba, Dixon?
他们在古巴会怎么对同性恋，Dixon？
They kill 'em!
会杀了他们！
Which, it might surprise you to learn, I am against.
怎么样，惊不惊喜，学到不少吧
I'm not sure if they do kill fagots down in Cuba, Dixon.
我不知道在古巴人是不是会残害同性恋，Dixon.
I know Cuba's human rights record is pretty deplorable
我只知道古巴的人权情况相当糟糕
when it comes to homosexuality, but killing 'em?
涉及到同性恋，就杀死他们？
Are you sure you ain't thinking of Wyoming?
你难道没有联想到怀俄明州？
Always with the smart-ass...- Jesus.
脑瓜倒是挺聪明...上帝
He's quite good, isn't he?
他挺不错，对吗？
Willoughby's a good man. Hey look at me.
Willoughby 是个好人。嘿，看着我。
Hey look at me. I'm talking nice to you now, am I?
嘿，看着我。 我正和你说话呢？
I'm talking nice to you.
我跟你好好说。
He shouldn't have this be the only thing he thinks about,
这事儿不应该成为他唯一的负担，
the last months left to him.
最后几个月时间留给他自己吧。
The last months what?
什么最后几个月？
Oh. You didn't know.
哦。你不知道啊。
Yeah. Pancreatic.
是胰腺癌。
I'm up next
我在这儿听着呢
if any of you ole ladies ever quit yakking.
你们还不如节省点胡扯的时间呢
- Rude. Hey Mildred.
- 没教养。嘿 Mildred。
Saw you on TV the other day.
那天我在电视上看到你了。
- Oh yeah? - Yeah, you looked good.
- 是吗？ 对，你看起来还不错。
I mean, y'know,
我的意思是，你懂得，
you came across really good, in the things you were saying.
对于遭遇的不幸，你挺过来了
I didn't think you came across really good in the things you were saying.
我觉得你还没走出来。
I thought you came across stupid-ass.
我感觉你像遇到了傻逼
Ain't it about time you got home to your momma, Dixon?
是回家找妈妈吃奶的时间了，Dixon
No it ain't time I got home to my momma.
不，还不到时候
I told her I was gonna be out 'til twelve. Actually.
我跟她说了，我会玩到12点。
Jesus!
上帝！
Me versus. You, Mildred!
咱俩来一局，Mildred!
Hey Robbie? I think that midget wants to get in my pants...
嘿 Robbie？我还以为那侏儒要钻到我裤子里…
Father Montgomery.
Montgomery教父。
Mildred. I'm sorry for calling on you so late, but.
Mildred。很抱歉这么晚来打扰你
I must say Robbie's been the consummate host.
Robbie招待地很好
Despite his having, he was just telling me, something of a tricky day at school.
不过他白天在学校遇到了些棘手的问题
Oh, no, just some of the guys on the team was giving me crap.
哦，不，只是一些人给我传闲话。
Crap about what? About the billboards, Mildred.
什么闲话？ 关于那些广告牌，Mildred。
Which is, uh, kind of what I've come to have a word with you about,
所以我想来和你说几句
Oh. Proceed.
哦。请继续。
I know how hard it's been for you, Mildred,
我知道这对你来说有多么艰难，Mildred，
this past year. We all do.
在过去的一年。大家都知道。
And if there's ever anything that you need,
如果有什么你需要的，
we'll be there for you. Always.
我们都会伸出援手。不论何时
But the town also knows what kind of a man William Willoughby is.
但镇上的人也都知道William Willoughby警长是个什么样的人。
And the town is dead set against these billboards of yours.
镇上都挺反对你的广告牌的。
Took a poll, did ya, Father?
你做民意调查了吗，教父？
You know Mildred, If you hadn't stopped coming to church,
Mildred，如果你来教堂看看
you'd had a little bit more understanding of the depth of people's feelings.
就会对大家的感受有点了解
I had more than a dozen people come up to me on Sunday.
礼拜日有十几个人到我这里来。
So, yes, I took a poll.
是的，我做了一个民意调查。
Everybody is with you...
每个人都支持同情你...
about Angela.
关于Angela.
Nobody is with you about this.
但在广告牌上，没有人站你这边。
Y'know what I was thinking about today?
你知道我今天都在想些什么吗？
I was thinking 'bout those street gangs they
我想到那些街头黑帮
got in Los Angeles, the Crips and the Bloods?
洛杉矶的Crips帮和Bloods帮
I was thinking about that buncha new laws they
我想到了那些新法规
came up with, in the 1980's I think it was,
我记得是在20世纪80年代提出，
to combat those street-gangs, those Crips and those Bloods.
为了打击街头黑帮 Crips 和 Bloods.
And, if I remember rightly, the gist of what those new laws were saying was
如果我没有记错的话，这些新法律的主旨是
if you join one of these gangs, and you're running with 'em,
如果你加入这些帮派，你和他们在一起，
and down the block from you one night, unbeknownst to you,
某个晚上，你们只是在一个街区闲逛，对你来说，啥都没发生
one of your fellow Crips, or your fellow Bloods, shoot up a place, or stab a guy,
但如果你的帮派中任何一员射击或刺伤一个人，
well, even though you didn't know nothing about it,
即便你对此一无所知，
even though you may've just been standing on
即使你站在那儿啥都没动
a streetcorner minding your own business,
一只是在街头盘算自己的生意
what these new laws said was
按照新的法规讲
you are still culpable.
你仍然有罪。
You are still culpable, by the very act of joining
加入帮派，你就是有罪的
those Crips, or those Bloods, in the first place.
Crips，或 Bloods，第一时间
Which got me thinking, Father,
让我联想到，教父
that whole type of situation is kinda like your Church boys, ain't it?
整个情况和你教堂里的子民很像，不是吗？
You've got your colors, you've got your clubhouse,
你有你的立场，你有你的居所，
you're, for want of a better word, a gang.
你们不过有一个比帮派更好的名字罢了。
And if you're upstairs smoking a pipe and reading a bible
如果你在楼上抽烟，读圣经
while one of your fellow gang members is downstairs fucking an altar boy then,
而你同伙中的一个正在在楼下借着献祭威胁一个男童呢，
Father, just like the Crips, and just like the Bloods,
教父，你就像Crips和Bloods帮派一样
you're culpable.
你是罪人。
Cos you joined the gang, man.
因为你加入了帮派。
And I don't care if you never did shit or never saw shit or never heard shit.
我不管是否见过、看过、听说过
You joined the gang.
只要加入了帮派。
You're culpable.
你就是有罪。
And when a person is culpable
当一个人是有罪的
to altar-boy-fucking, or anykinda-boy-fucking,
猥亵献祭男童，或其他污辱行为
I know you guys didn't really narrow it down,
我知道你们并没有想把事情掩盖住，
, then they kinda forfeit the right to come into my house and say
但他们没有权利进入我家，对我指手画脚
anything about me, or my life, or my daughter, or my billboards.
任何关于我，我的生活，或我的女儿，或我的广告。
So, why don't you just finish your tea there,
所以，你为什么不赶紧喝完茶，
Father, and get the fuck outta my kitchen.
从我的厨房滚出去呢？教父
But thanks for coming up anyway, Father.
还是谢谢你能过来，教父。
How you been feeling, Bill?
Bill，你感觉怎么样？
Oh, like I got cancer in a major organ.
哦，就像我的重要器官得了癌症一样。
Well I just want you to know, we're all on your side about this Mildred Hayes thing...
我只说，我们都站你这边，关于Mildred Hayes做的那些事...
If I have to hear that one more fucking time...!
他们的我还要在听一遍吗...！
I'm done with this shit. I can't waste my life waiting.
我受够了。我不能再浪费生命一直等着了。
Stop reading fucking comics and Get me the file on the Hayes case.
别他妈的看漫画，把Hayes案子的档案给我
The Angela Hayes case or the Mildred Hayes case?
是 Angela Hayes 还是Mildred Hayes？
There is no Mildred Hayes case.
这没Mildred Hayes的案子。
We've had two official complaints about the billboards, so, actually...
我们收到了两个关于广告牌的正式投诉，所以
From who?
谁投诉的？
A lady with a funny eye...
一位眼神有趣的女士
and a fat dentist.
还有一个胖胖的牙医。
Give me the file on the Angela Hayes case.
给我 Angela Hayes案件的档案。
“A lady with a funny fucking eye”,
“一位眼神有趣的女士”，
Jesus Christ.
上帝。
Late night?
又熬夜了？
No.
没有。
Lay off that Welby guy.
别管Welby那家伙了
Or you'll do what?
不然你会怎样？
Or I'll kick your fucking Momma's teeth in.
不然我他妈把你牙踢掉
No you won't.
不，你不会的。
Who told ya I was laying on him anyway? The midget?
谁告诉你，我找他事儿了？ 那个侏儒？
What the fuck are you talking about?!
你他妈的在说什么？
I'm trying to fucking concentrate! Fucking midgets!
我正在集中精力思考！去他妈的侏儒！
What are you looking for, anyway?
你在找什么呢？
There's nothing to look for.
没有什么可找的。
I don't know what it is.
我不知道怎么了
This feels like it's kinda waggling.
就是觉得有点摇晃了。
Well if it's waggling it's gonna have to come out.
那么如果摇晃了，就必须得拔出来。
Ain't you gonna have a look at it first?
你不先看一下吗？
It's gonna have to come out.
必须得拔出来。
Uh, can I get a little Novocaine, there, Doc?
呃，我能上点麻醉药吗，医生？
Give it a couple minutes.
等几分钟。
I just wanted to say...There's a lotta good friends
我只是想说...
of Bill Willoughby in this town, Mrs.Hayes,
Bill Willoughby在镇上有很多好朋友，Hayes
No! Ouch! Stop it! No, god!
草！哎哟!快住手！妈的，上地！！
Goddamit.
我操
Then why don't you tell those good friends of Bill Willoughby
那你为什么和Bill Willoughby的那些好朋友说说
to tell him to go do his fucking job, fat boy.
让他好好干他妈的工作啊，小胖砸。
Hey there, Mildred!
嘿，Mildred!
You didn't happen to pay a visit to the dentist today, did ya?
你今天没有碰巧去看牙医吧？
- No.- Huh?
- 没有 - 呃？
I Said 'No'.
我说了没去'。
Oh. So it wasn't you who drilled a little hole in one of
哦。所以，不是你
big fat Geoffrey's big fat thumbnails, no?
在大胖子 Geoffrey的大拇指上钻了个洞，是吗？
Of course not.
当然不是我。
- Huh. I said “Of course not.”
- 呃。 我说“不是我”
You drilled a hole in the dentist?
你在牙医身上钻了一个洞？
No, Denise, I didn't.
不，Denise，我没有。
- Well, I thought it was kinda funny myself, but
- 好吧，我自己也觉得有点滑稽，但是
he wants to press charges, so we're gonna have to bring you in, I'm afraid.
他想要控告你，所以恐怕我们得先来把你请进去。
So how's it all going in the nigger torturing business, Dixon?
在折磨黑奴的事儿上你们干得怎么样了？Dixon?
It's 'Persons of color'-torturing business, these days,
是虐待有色人种
if you want to know.
如果你想知道。
And I didn't torture nobody.
我没有虐待任何人。
What's the matter with you, saying that goddam stuff on TV.
你在电视上说的是什么玩意
My momma watches that station!
我妈看了那个台！
Your momma does not know about the torturing?
你妈妈不知道什么是虐待？
No she didn't know anything about it.She's against that kinda thing.
不，她什么都不知道。她反对那种事情。
Who's against that kinda thing?
谁反对这种事情？
Who's against what? My momma. Is against 'Persons-of-color torturing'.
谁反对什么？我妈妈是反对“有色人种酷刑”。
She said 'nigger-torturing'. I said you can't say 'nigger-torturing' no more.
她说“黑鬼酷刑”。我说你不能再说“黑鬼酷刑”了。
You gotta say 'Persons-of-color' torturing.
你得说有色人种酷刑。
Isn't that right, Chief?
长官，这样对吗？
I think I'll be able to take care of Mrs.Hayes  on my own from here on, Jason.
我自己能搞定Hayes，Jason.
Sure, Chief, I'll be right outside.
好的，掌柜，我会在外面等着。
Don't gimme that look.
不要用那种表情看我。
If you got rid of every cop with vaguely racist leanings then you'd have
如果你把每个有种族歧视的警察都开了，那你就
three cops left and all o'them are gonna hate the fags
只剩下三个警察了，而且这三还歧视同性恋
so what are ya gonna do, y'know?
所以你会怎么做，你懂了吗？
I wanna know something,Mildred...
我想了解一些情况，Mildred...
Why'd ya drill a hole thru
为什么你在在可怜的 Geoffrey's
poor fat Geoffrey's thumbnail?
大拇指上钻一个洞？
That didn't happen.
我没干。
His hand slipped and he drilled a hole thru his self.
他手滑了一下，自己给自己钻的。
Did he say I did it?
他说是我干的了吗？
I guess it's just his word against mine, then huh?
我想他只是想针对我吧
Kinda like in all those rape cases you hear about.
有点像你听过强奸案
Except, this time,
这次不一样，
the chick ain't losing.
我可不是任人宰割的小鸡。
It ain't really about winning or losing, though,
这不是关于赢或者输，
is it, Mildred?
是吗？Mildred?
I mean, do you think I care about who wins or loses between the two of yous?
我的意思是，你认为我关心你们之间的胜负吗？
Do you think I care about dentists?
你以为我在乎牙医吗
I don't care about dentists.
我不在乎牙医。
Nobody cares about dentists!
没有人关心牙医
What I I do care about, or what I'm
我所关心的
interested in,
或感兴趣的
is tying you up in court so long
是把你拴在法庭时间够长
that your hours at the gift shop are so shot to shit
你在礼品店的工作时间就不够了
that you ain't got a penny to pay for another months billboards.
你就没有钱可以支付另一个月的广告牌了。
That's what I'm interested in.
这是我感兴趣的。
I got some dough put away...
我可是有些私房钱的
What I heard was you had to sell off your ex-husband's
我说是你必须卖掉你前夫的
tractor-trailer to even pay for this month's billboards, that right?
拖拉机来支付本月的广告牌，对吗？
How is ole Charlie, by the way?
哦，Charlie怎么样了，顺便问下？
He still shacked up with that pretty little intern works down at the zoo?
他还在那个在动物园里混着实习生的岗位？
He's still shacked up with some chick who smells of shit.
他仍然整天和那些满是鸡屎味的鸡呆着。
I don't know if the zoo's got anything to do with it.
我不知道动物园是否会改善情况。
Although I'd hope so.
虽然我希望如此。
How old is she?
她多大了？
Nineteen? That's smart.
十九？这很聪明。
Keep trying,
接着问啊，
Keep trying.
接着问
What's Charlie think about these here billboards of yours,
Charlie看到你这些广告牌会怎么想
an ex-cop like Charlie?
像Charlie这样当过警察的？
Ex-cop, ex-wife-beater. Same difference, I guess, right?
当过警察，家暴过前妻。没什么两样把，我说？
His word against yours, though, right?
你们总是彼此反对，对吗？
Charlie don't know about them, does he?
查理不知道，对吗？
It's none of his business.
这不关他的事。
He's kinda paying for'em though, ain't he?
但是他在付钱，不是吗？
I'm paying for 'em.
是我花的钱。
This month you are. How about when...
这个月是你。那下个..
- I didn't mean to...- I know...
我不是故意的 我知道...
- It was an accident... I know, baby.
- 这是个意外  我知道，亲爱的。
It's blood.
这是血。
I'll go get somebody...
我去找人
Hey!
嘿!
Just let her go.- C'mon Chief.
让她走吧- 不是吧 长官
Just let her go!
让她走吧！
Easy, easy, easy.
放松 放松 放松。
Hey.
嘿。
Do birds get cancer?
鸟类会得癌症吗？
- Huh?- Birds. Do they get cancer?
- 呃？ - 鸟。他们得癌症吗？
I don't know. Dogs do.
我不知道。但狗会。
Yeah, well, I wasn't talking about dogs, was I?
是啊，但我不是在说狗
Great.
真棒。
The good ole “Raped While Dying” route home.
很好的“强奸而死”回家路。
Cos if there was two seconds in a day when I didn't think about her,
一天中我有那么两秒不想起她
and wasn't thinking about how she died, “.
不想她是怎么死的
There ya go, think about it some more, why don't ya?”
广告牌就来了，快多回想下
It's good, too, that as much as a person might've
这很好，有的人
tried to avoid the details of what happened,
不想了解事情的细节，
cos he didn't think it'd do any good, and he didn't think he could bear it,
因为他认为这没有什么好处，他可能承受不了，
it's also good to be informed in twenty foot high font and a real nice lettering,
这真棒，二十英尺高的字母，字体也很漂亮
the precise details of her last moments.
还有她最后的细节。
That it wasn't enough that she was raped,
被强奸是不够的，
and it wasn't enough that she died, no.
死了也不够的，
“Raped While Dying”.
“强奸而死”。
Thank you, mom.
妈妈，谢谢你。
I gave you the police reports...
我给你的警察报告
I didn't read 'em!
我没有读过！
I'm depressed enough as it fucking is!
我已经够郁闷了！
Mom!
妈妈！
Yeah?
怎么了？
You ain't going out again tonight, are ya?
你今晚不出去了，是吗？
Denise and I are gonna grab a couple of beers, yeah.
Denise和我要去喝几杯啤酒
Denise gonna be driving ya?
丹妮斯要开车吗？
Angela, why don't you just ask
me if you can borrow the car?
安吉拉，你为什么不直接问我能不能借下车？
- Can I borrow the car?- No.
- 我可以借下车吗？- 不行
Bitch!
婊子！
I'll give you money for a taxi
我会给你钱打出租的
if you ask me nice and don't call me a bitch.
如果你问好好问我，不要叫我婊子。
Why did you make me ask you borrow it if you was never gonna let me borrow it?
为什么你一开始都没打算借还让我开口问？
Cos it was funny. And cos you've been smoking pot all day.
因为这很有趣。因为你一整天都在吸烟
- You are such a hypocrite!'Hypocrite, '
- 你真是个伪君子！ “伪君子”
How?
怎么了？
You drove drunk with us in the car when we was kids.
当我们还是小孩的时候，你还醉驾开车。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Daddy told me.
爸爸告诉我的
- When did you see him? don't change the subject.
- 你什么时候见到他的？不要转移主题。
Did you or did you not drive drunk with us in the car when we was kids?
我们还是小的时候，你还是不是载着我们醉驾了？
Once. Maybe.
就一次。也许。
Oh, 'once, ' okay...
呵呵，就一次，好吧...
...when he was in the middle of beating the shit out of me...
当时他快把我打死了...
Which we've only got your word about, right?
这是你的一面之词，对吧？
Angela, For Christ's sake...
Angela，上帝
Oh why are you never on my side, Robbie?
你为什么从不站在我这边，Robbie?
I'm always on your side when you're not being a cunt.
当你不那么事儿逼的时候，我一直都站你这边啊。
- Hey!- Hey!
- 嘿！- 嘿！
There'll be no more 'Cunts' in this house, you got that, Mister?
这屋里不许再提“逼”，知道了吗，哥们？
What, are you moving out?
怎么，你要搬出去？
It was a gag!
那只是个玩笑！
So are ya gonna let me borrow the car or what?
那你到底让不让我借车？
Why don't you just walk, Angela?
你为什么不走路，Angela?
- Why don't you just walk?
- You know what,
- 你为什么不走路？
- 你知道吗，
I will walk,
我会走，
I will walk. And y'know what?
我会走。你知道吗？
I hope I get raped on the way.
但愿我在路上被强奸了。
Yeah? Well I hope you get raped on the way too!
是吗？那我祝你心想事成
We're gonna need to keep you in a few days, Bill.
比尔，你要留院观察几天。
You shouldn't be coughing up blood.
你不应该咳嗽血液。
Yeah, I kinda guessed that, Doc.
好，我猜到了，医生。
I'll swing by in the morning. Anne.
我早上会来查房。 Anne.
Anne.
安妮。
Guess I'll go get your coat, huh?
猜到我会去拿你的外套了吧？
- Well you know I ain't staying...- And you know I ain't arguing.
- 那么你知道我住不下的...- 你知道我不会劝你的。
You... old... cunt.
你…个老... 骚
I'm not old, Robbie.
我不老，Robbie.
That's Dad!
是爸爸！
Hey dad! How's it going?
嘿老爸！怎么样了？
Where's the crazy lady...?
那个疯女人在哪？
The kid's got Rice fucking Krispies in his fucking hair!
孩子头上怎么她妈的都是麦片！
What's going on around here?And what the fuck's
这里发生了什么？
going on with these fucking billboards, Mildred?
那些广告牌是她妈怎么回事，Mildred?
- Kinda self-explanatory, ain't it? - Well why don't you just explain it to me?
- 有点不言自明，不是吗？- 那么你为什么不解释下呢？
Guess it ain't self-explanatory then.
我想这不需要解释。
Well, y'know, I guess I wanted certain people's
好吧，我只是想让某些人
minds kept on certain people's jobs, is all.
集中精力办正事，就这样
I hadn't heard a word from 'em in seven goddam months, but I tell ya this,
我这7个月都没听他们说一句案子的事儿，但是我告诉你，
I heard an awful lot from 'em since I put those billboards up...
自从我把这些广告牌放上去以后，他们和我说了不少
You think this has focused their minds?
你认为这样就让他们集中精力了?
I'll tell you what it's focused their minds on. It's focused
我来告诉你他们都在集中精力干啥。
their minds on how exactly are they gonna fuck you up.
他们都在集中精力怎搞你呢，他妈的。
The more you keep a case in the public eye,
你把一个案子曝光唉在公众视线下越多，
the better your chancesof getting it solved,
解决问题的机会越大，
it's in all the guidebooks, Charlie.
Charlie 指导手册上都有写。
How much those billboards cost?
这些广告牌花了多少钱？
Bout the same as a tractor-trailer.
那辆拖拉机的价格。
- What the fuck are you laughing at?- Nothing.
- 他妈的你在笑什么？- 没什么。
Laughed at by a guy with fucking cereal in his hair!
被一个头上粘屎的人笑话
How is Penelope?
Penelope怎么样了？
- Huh? She's alright. - Why don't you invite her in,
- 呃？她没事- 你为什么不邀她进屋，
- save leaving her sitting out there? - She's here?
- 让她自己在外面等？- 她来了？
- She's out in the car. - Oh. That explains it.
- 她在车里。- 哦。难怪呢。
- That explains what?- I knew I smelled something.
- 什么难怪呢？- 我说我闻到什么骚味了。
Let her go.
放开她。
Oh, um, I kinda needed to use the bathroom,
呃，我想用卫生间，
but if it's inconvenient, actually
但如果实在不方便的话
it is inconvenient, isn't it, I can see it's
不太方便，对吗，看起来
inconvenient, I can hold it, it's alright...
不方便的话，我可以憋会儿，没问题的...
- It's the first door, down the hall. - Are you sure? I feel like I'm
- 在大厅里的第一扇门。 -确定没问题？
- intruding... - Just go pee!
- 我觉得好像侵犯了… - 快去尿吧！
OK.
好的。
Look, you've said what you came to say.
要说的你都说完了。
Okay? Why don't ya just go get zoo girl and get the hell out of my house? Alright?
没事儿了？带上你的动物园女孩，滚出去？好吗？
Um, actually, zoo-wise,
嗯，实际上，动物园方面，
they were letting people go at the zoo, unfortunately,
不幸的是，动物园确实裁员了
and it was a case of “Last in, first out”, so, yeah,
而且是不留新人的政策，所以
unfortunately the zoo had to let me go.
动物园不得不让我走。
But they were looking for people down at the horse-rides
但他们正在为马场招人
for the disabled's, to look after the horses down there,
为残疾人照看马匹，
so I'm working down there now,
所以我现在还在那工作，
looking after the disabled's horses,
照顾残疾人的马，
Don't say a word.
别说话。
I wasn't gonna say a word.
我不会说一句
You don't think I don't wish it had never happened?!
你以为我不希望这事儿从没发生吗？
You don't think I don't wish she was still here
你以为我不希望她还活着吗
I know you do.
我知道你希望
我知道。
Billboards ain't gonna bring her back, Mildred.
广告牌不会让她回来，Mildred.
Neither is fucking nineteen year olds, Charlie.
查理，他们又不是只有十九岁。
Yeah.
是啊。
But I know that.
但我知道。
Just go.
走吧。
Yeah, alright,
是的，好吧，
I'm such a shitty dad and you're such a great mom. Alright.
我是一个不称职的爸爸，你是一个很棒的母亲。
So how come
那为什么
a week before she died she comes around asking
她死前一个星期，她来问我
if she can move in with me at my place,
她能不能搬去我那儿住
cos she couldn't stand the two of yous bitching at each other no more,
因为她受不了你们两个互骂婊子
- and fighting with each other no more.. - I don't believe you...
- 整日争吵了.. 我不相信你
And I said “No, stay at home, your mom loves you.”
我说：“不行，留在家里，妈妈爱你。”
And now I wish I hadn't,
而现在我希望我没那么说，
cos if I hadn't she'd still fucking be here!
因为如果我那样，她也许还会在这里！
- I don't believe you! - Don't believe me.
我不相信你- 不要相信我。
Ask Fruit Loop boy.
问下麦片小子啊。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
I don't know, mom.
妈妈我不知道
Yeah, you do.
是的，你知道。
Oh come on
哦，来吧
Donald Sutherland again! What is this, a freaking Donald Sutherland season?!
又是Donald Sutherland 这是什么，Donald Sutherland 专属季？
I like him.
我喜欢他。
I like his hair.- Hair.
我喜欢他的头发。头发。
This is the one where his little girl dies.
这是他小女孩去世的地方。
Always a plus in a movie!
总是加在电影中！
Talking of dead kids,
说到死去的孩子，
what's happening with the Billboard lady?
那位广告女士是怎么回事？
Oh that booze won't listen to reason.
哦，她不听任何理由
She's as tough as an old boot!
和老靴子一样顽固！
Oh. Why don't you just fuck her over thru her friends then?
哦。你为什么不通过她的朋友搞定她呢？
- Huh.- Y'know,
- 呃。- 你懂得，
why don't you fuck her friends over? Bring her around out way.
你为什么不从她朋友下手？把她抓起来。
Has she got some friends you could fuck over?
她总有一些朋友可以下手吧？
Bastard.
混蛋。
Hey fuckhead?!
嘿 他妈的？
- What? - Don't say 'What', Dixon,
- 什么？ - 别说“什么”，Dixon,
when she comes in calling you a fuckhead, and don't you come in here...
当她进来叫你他妈的，你不许进来...
- Shut up!
- 闭嘴！
- You! Get over here. - No.
- 你！过来  没门
You get over here.
你过来
- Alright...- What?! Don't... Dixon!
- 好的...- 什么？！别...Dixon !
What?! I'm taking care of this!
什么？！我在管这事儿！
- You do not allow a member of the public tocall you a fuckhead in the station house!
- 不能纵容他人在警局的公众场所叫你他妈的！
That's what I'm doing, I'm taking care of it! In my own way. Actually.
我在管这事儿，我正在按自己的方法处理。
Now get out of my ass! Mrs. Hayes.
别他们管我的事儿！ Hayes.太太
Grab a seat. What is it I can do for you today?
随便坐 今儿需要我帮什么忙吗？
Where's Denise Watson?
Denise Watson在哪儿？
- Denise Watson's in the Clank.- On what charge?
- 她被捕了-什么罪名？
- Possession.- Of what?
- 非法持有。- 什么？
Two marijuana cigarettes. Big ones.
两根大麻香烟。够大的案子了
- When's the bail hearing? - I asked the Judge not to give her bail
- 什么时候保释听证会？- 我让法官不要保释
on account of her previous marijuana violations and the Judge said sure.
因为她以前有大麻违规记录，法官同意了。
You fucking prick.
你他妈的。
You do not call an officer of the law
你不给律师打个电话吗？
a fucking prick in his own station-house, Mrs. Hayes.
她正一个人在审讯室呢。 Hayes.夫人
Or anywhere, actually.
或者别的地方
What's with the new hard-boiled attitude, Dixon?
Dixon，你这新面孔哪儿学的？
Your momma been coaching ya?
你妈妈教你的？
No. My momma doesn't do that.
不，不是我妈妈交的。
Take 'em down,
把他们放下，
you hear me?
你听到了吗？
You did good, Dixon.
好样的，Dixon.
Yeah, I know I did.
是的，我知道我做到了。
Now, the rules here are twofold;
现在，有两条规则。
no kid
孩子们
can leave this goddam blanket at any goddam time,
任何情况相爱都不准离开这块毯子，
and every single one of these dolls and these teddy bears
这些娃娃和泰迪熊
has gotta be hooked up.
必须串在一起来。
Now, your momma and I,
现在，你的妈妈和我，
although it won't look like it, we'll be watching every goddam move you make
虽然看起来不像，但会顶着你们的一举一动
and the most important thing while we're watching you
什么重要的事儿我们都看着
is you do not leave this blanket.
不要离开这条毯子
The next most important thing is you do not
其次最重要的是
at any stage
任何情况下
allow the fishing rods to stick into you or your sister's eyeballs,
不要让让钓鱼竿戳进你或你妹妹的眼球里，
as this would be counter-productive to the entire operation.
因为这将破坏整个活动。
What would this be?
我说了什么？
Counterproductive to the entire operation.
因为这将破坏整个活动。
Then troops...
然后小分队...
start fishing.
开始钓鱼吧。
We. Are. Not.
我们。是。不。
We are.
我们是。
Hey, baby.
嗨宝贝。
Yeah!
好吧！
Still no arrests.
仍然没被捕。
How come, I wonder?
怎么办到的，我想知道？
Cos there ain't no God and the world's empty
因为没有上帝，世界是空虚的
and it don't matter what we do to each other?
我们对对方做什么也并不重要？
Ooh, I hope not.
哦，我希望不是这样。
How comes you came up here outta nowhere, looking so pretty?
你怎么凭空出现的？看起来很漂亮
You ain't trying to make me believe in eincarnation or something, are ya?
你不是想让我相信轮回之类吧，是吗？
Well, you're pretty, but you ain't her.
虽然你很漂亮，但你不是她。
She got killed,
她被杀了，
and now she's dead forever.
现在她永远去了。
I do thank you for coming up, though.
不过，我很感谢你的到来。
If I had some food I'd give it ya,
如果我有一些食物，我会把它给你，
but I've only got some Doritos and It might kill ya, they're kinda pointy.
但我只吃了一些玉米片，可能会杀了你，他们有点硬。
Then where would we be?
我们死后会去哪儿？
Oh, Mildred.
哦，Mildred.
Yeah, so I
是的，我
uh, just happened to be looking over our contract we drew up
呃，恰好正在审查我们那时制定的合同
back that time, and what I realized was,
我意识到，
I realized that although payment is to be made
我意识到，虽然付款是要在
on the first day of each month,
在每个月的第一天，
the first payment you paid was actually a deposit,
你付的第一笔付款实际上是一笔押金，
wasn't it, like we said, so actually, in point of fact, you're actually
所以事实上，你已经
behind in your payments now, by,
拖欠了一部分款项
yeah, a month.
额，一个月了。
Yeah. That's, uh,
嗯。那是
what the contract says. Looking it over an' all.
合同上也这么写的。你可以全都看下
The lawyer says so too.
法务也这么说。
When do you need this next payment by, Red?
你什么时候需要下次付款？Red
Uh, well, now, really.
呃，现在就需要，真的。
Or... Fuh uh... Friday?
或者...呃...星期五？
Wow.
哇。
When you can't trust the lawyers and the advertising men,
你连律师和广告人都不能信任了
what the hell's America coming to, huh?
美国到底是怎么了？
Who got to ya Red?
谁指示干的？Red？
Willoughby?
- Nobody got to me.- My fat fucking ass!
没人让我这么干 - 我的天
He's dying, Mildred.
他快死了，Mildred.
We're all fucking dying!
我们都是要死了！
Red?
Oh, hi Pamela! Um, we're a little bit busy, at the moment,
噢，害 Pamela! 嗯，我们现在有点忙
Pam, if that's okay...
Pam，如果可以的话...
Oh Red, I know, and I know you were real anxious
哦，Red，我知道，我知道你真的很焦虑
about talking to Mrs. Hayes this morning and all...
今天早上要和海耶斯太太说清楚
Anxious? No.
焦急？没有。
But that's the thing, there's no need to be, cos you won't believe it!
但是没有必要了，因为你不会相信！
A little Mexican delivery boy just dropped in with this...
一个小墨西哥的快递员刚刚送来了这个.
What the hell's this?!
这是什么？！
- I know! It's five thousand dollars! And guess what
- 我知道！这是五千美元！ 你猜怎么着
the note says? It says it's to pay for the rental on Mrs. Hayes's billboards!
备注说这是为了支付Hayes夫人的广告牌的租金！
Can you believe it? That's why I butted in!
你相信吗？所以我才强行插入一嘴
- Well, who's it from? - Well, it doesn't say.
- 那是从谁那寄来的？- 好吧，上面没说。
Well, where's the delivery boy?
那么送货员呢？
Well, he went.
那他走了。
- Well, did you see what company he was from?
- 呃，你知道他是公司来的吗？
- Well, no.- Well, what kinda uniform did he have on?
- 不知道。- 他穿什么样的制服？
Well, he just looked like one of those fat little Mexican boys.
他看起来就像那些胖乎乎的小墨西哥男孩一样。
On a bicycle?
骑自行车？
Did I do something wrong? - No, Pam, you did good.
我做错什么了吗？- 不，Pam，你做得很好。
Yeah, Pam, you did real good.
是的，帕姆，你真的很好。
Did I? Great!
我有吗？太棒了！
Ain't life crazy?
生活不就是这么疯狂吗？
What's the note say Red?
备注上写了什么？
Says, er,
说，呃，
“This here money is to go towards the fund for Mildred Hayes's billboards,
“这里的钱是为了 Mildred Haye 的广告牌的基金，
cos she ain't the only one found here who hates the pigs.
因为她不是唯一一个恨蠢猪的人。
Signed, a friend.”
签名 朋友 。“
Jeez, I guess ya can't be picky who your friends are these days, huh?
哎呀，我猜这些日子你交朋友都不挑剔了吧？
Um, I guess I'll be needing a receipt off ya Red,
嗯，我想需要一份收据
y'know, saying the price of next month's is paid in full an' all.
下个月的价格是全额支付的。
Oh. Sure, Mildred, sure.
哦。当然，Mildred，当然。
Yeah. Like, now.
是啊。像现在。
Oh! Sure!
哦!当然！
Is mommy drunk, daddy?
妈妈醉了，爸爸？
No, no, she's just got a little migraine, that's all.
不，不，她只是有点偏头痛，就是这样。
A little Chardonnay migraine,
一点偏头痛，
now no more chit chat out of you two, ok?
现在你们两个不许闲聊了，知道吗？
Can we stay home from school again tomorrow, daddy?
爸爸，明天我们呆在家不去上学吗？
We'll see what your mommy says in the morning, darling...
我们看看你妈妈早上怎么说亲爱的...
Aww!
噢！
Eyes close.
闭上眼睛。
Then go to sleep, ok?
然后去睡觉，好吗？
You don't smell of puke.
你没有酒吐的气味。
Which is good.
真不错。
Aquafresh. Trick I learned.
是牙膏。我也学了点小窍门
Women, huh?
女人，是吧？
It's still your turn to clean the horseshit outta the stable, y'know?
现在轮到你把马厩打扫干净了
Those fucking horses!
去他妈的马！
They're your fucking horses! I'm gonna have those fucking horses shot!
他们是你的马！我会把马射杀了！
I'll do it,
我会去做的，
you lazy bitch.
你个懒惰的小婊子。
Thank you, poppa.
谢谢你， poppa.
That was a real nice day.
那真是一个愉快的一天。
And that was a real nice fuck.
而且真是一场非常好的性爱。
You got a real nice cock, Mr. Willoughby.
Mr. Willoughby.你有一个不错的的好鸟。
Is that from a play,
这是戏剧台词吗，
“You got a real nice cock, Mr. Willoughby?” I think.
你有一只好鸟，Mr. Willoughby？
I heard it in a Shakespeare one time.
我曾经在莎士比亚戏剧里听过一次。
You dummy.
你个傻瓜。
It's Oscar Wilde.
是奥斯卡·王尔德。
"Oscar Wilde."
“奥斯卡·王尔德。”
My darling Anne.
亲爱的 Anne.
There's a longer letter in the dresser drawer
梳妆台抽屉里有一封长信
I've been writing for the last week or so.
上星期我一直在写
That one covers us,
那里有我们
and my memories of us,
和我的回忆，
and how much I've always loved you.
还有我多么爱你
This one just covers tonight,
这封只说今晚，
and, more importantly, today.
更重要的是，今天。
Tonight I have gone out to the horses to end it.
今晚我到马厩自杀
I cannot say sorry for the act itself,
我不能为这件事道歉，
although I know that for a short time you will be angry at me
虽然我知道很短的时间你会生我的气
or even hate me for it.
甚至恨我。
Please don't.
请不要。
This is not a case of “I came in this world alone,
这不是“我独自来到这个世界，
and I'm going out of it alone” or anything dumb like that.
我独自离开“或类似的心灵鸡汤
I did not come in this world alone, my mom was there,
我不是一个人来到这个世界，我的母亲在世上，
and I am not going out of it alone,
而且我不是一个人走的，
cos you are there,
因为你就在那里，
drunk on the couch,
醉倒在沙发上，
making Oscar Wilde cock jokes.
说着奥斯卡王尔德的鸡巴笑话。
No. This is a case, in some senses, of bravery.
不，这是一种勇敢。
Not the bravery of facing a bullet down;
不是面对子弹的勇气;
the next few months of pain would be far harder
接下来的几个月的疼痛会更加剧烈
than that small flash.
现在只是星星之火
No, it's the bravery of weighing up
不，这是权衡的勇气
the next few months of still being with you,
接下来的几个月还要和你在一起，
still waking up with you,
醒来在你身边，
of playing with the kids,
和孩子们一起玩，
against the next few months of seeing in your eyes
接下来的几个月看着你的眼睛
how much my pain is killing you;
我的疼痛会一步步摧残你;
how my weakened body as it ebbs away
我身体日渐衰退，
and you tend to it are your final and lasting memories of me.
这会是你你对我的最终和永久的记忆。
I won't have that.
我不想要这样
Your final memories of me will be us at the riverside,
你对我的最后记忆将是我们在河边，
and that dumb fishing game
那愚蠢的钓鱼游戏
which I think they cheated at,
不过我觉得她们作弊了
and me inside of you, and you on top of me,
我进入你的身体，而你在我上面
and barely a fleeting thought
对于未来的黑暗
of the darkness yet to come.
没有一点念头。
That was the best, Anne.
Anne. 那是最好的。
A whole day of not thinking about it.
一整天没有想到它。
Dwell on this day, baby, cos it was the best day of my life.
宝贝，因为这一天是生命中最美好的一天。
Kiss the girls for me,
亲吻我的女孩，
and know that I've always loved you,
你知道我一直爱着你，
and maybe I'll see you again if there's another place.
如果还有另一个地方，我可能会再次见到你。
And if there ain't,
如果没有，
well, it's been Heaven knowing you.
那你肯定是去了天堂。
Your boy...
你的男孩...
...Bill.
What the Hell's going on around here?
他妈的发生什么了？
What?
什么？
Can you stand now?
你能站好吗？
I can stand
我能站好
I'd better get out there,
我最好走出去，
say something to 'em.
对他们说些什么。
You ain't gonna faint again, are ya?
你不会晕倒，是吗？
I know... that the best thing,
我知道...最好的事情，
the only thing,
唯一的事情，
to honor that man's memory right now,
为了纪念那个男人
is to go to work.
是去上班。
Is to be a
是成为一个
good cop.
好警察。
Is to walk in his shoes.
传说他的鞋子。
Is to do what he did, every day of his life.
做他一生中每一天都做的事。
Help people.
帮助他人。
What the hell is going on?
这她妈怎么回事？
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
You fucking pig!
滚你妈的猪头！
What the fuck are you doing?!
你他妈在干什么？！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
See, Red?
看看，Red？
I got issues with white folks too...
我也遇到了白人问题
The fuck are you looking at?
你他妈的在看啥？
Reports, sadly, have come in overnight,
报道一起不幸案件，
that Chief William Willoughby of Ebbing, Missouri,
密苏里州 Ebbing 镇的警长 William Willoughby
took his own life early this morning in the grounds of his home.
今天早上在他家方自杀了。
This report just in from Gabriella Forrester.
来自 Gabriella Forrester的报道。
Tragedy came calling today upon this quiet family home
悲剧今天降临到这个安静的家庭
outside of Ebbing, Missouri;
密苏里州 Ebbing镇
a home belonging to Chief William Willoughby,
William Willoughby 警长的家里，
his wife, Anne, their two young daughters, Polly and Jane.
他的妻子Anne,，他们两个年轻的女儿Polly and Jane.
What appears to be a self-inflicted gunshot wound
貌似是自杀的枪伤
brought life to an end for Chief Willoughby,
带走了Willoughby的生命
a man highly respected in Ebbing
一个在Ebbing镇深受中尊敬的人
for his diligence and his service to the community,
他对社区服务非常勤奋，
What led him to take his life in the early hours of this morning
是什么导致他在今天凌晨的结束生命
it is too early to speculate;
现在下定论为时尚早;
there were rumors of illness;
有传言说有疾病;
could it simply have been the pressure of the job;
或者只是工作的压力？
or could it have something to do with a story we ran here just two weeks ago,
还是可能跟我们两个星期前在这里报道的故事有关？
of these billboards, and the woman who put them there,
那些广告牌和挂广告的女人，
...Mildred Hayes.
Mildred Hayes。
Don't. Don't.
别。别。
Hey there.
嘿。
Do you know who threw that can?
你知道谁扔的易拉罐吗？
What can?
什么易拉罐？
How about you, sweetheart? Do you know who threw that can?
亲爱的，你知道呢？
你知道谁扔的吗？
Uh, no, I didn't really see...
呃不，我真的没看见...
Thank you mom.
妈妈，谢谢你。
And what can I do for you today, Sir?
先生，我今天能为您做些什么？
What's your name?
你叫什么名字？
Name's on my tag, man.
名字在我的标签，先生。
You hard of reading?
你有阅读困难吗？
Hard of reading
阅读困难？
no, no. That's good, “hard of reading”. It's kind of like “hard of hearing”,
不，不。不是“阅读困难”，是听力障碍吧
but it's actually it's “hard of reading',
但实际上它是“难读”的，
it's like a play on words or something huh.
这像在玩文字游戏或绕口令
What do you want?
你想做什么？
Uh, I've been sent down to uh, take over from.
呃，我被派到这里接班。
Chief Willoughby, in light of last night's unfortunate event.
鉴于昨晚Willoughby警长的不幸事件
You have got to be fucking kidding me!
你他妈的是在开玩笑吧！
Do you have any documentation to prove that, Sir?
先生，你有任何证明文件吗？
You really wanna see my documentation, fucker?
你真的想看我的档案，笨蛋？
Yeah, see his documentation!
是啊，看他的档案！
Should make him show it to you.
让他展示给你看下。
None of you cracker motherfuckers got no work to do?
你们都没事儿可干吗？
Ain't that racialist?
那不是种族主义吗？
What happened to your hands, Officer Dixon?
Dixon警官，你怎么了？
Oh, I just kinda
哦，我只是有点
banged 'em up a little bit while I was throwing
我把某人扔出窗口时，
some guy out of a fucking window. Y'know,
受了点伤。
the usual.- Oh yeah?
常有的事儿。- 是吗？
They never taught me that one at the Academy.
我在学院从来没被这样教过。
Which fucking Academy you go to?
你上的哪个学院？
How's things coming along on the Angela Hayes case?
Angela Hayes案件的进展如何？
How's things coming along on the 'Mind your own fucking business' case?
“少管闲事”你一点都学不会吗？
How things coming along on the hand me your gun and your badge?
交出你的枪和警徽怎么样？
- Huh?- Hand me your gun and your badge.
- 呃？- 给我你的枪和你的警徽。
Shit.
我日。
I can't find my badge.
找不到我的警徽了。
No, seriously. Maybe I lost it
真的。也许我弄丢了
or dropped it when I was doing the window guy?
或者我在从窗户扔人时它扔掉了？
Just get out of my station house, man.
滚出我的警局，伙计
What's going on?
怎么回事？
I think I just got fired.
我刚刚被解雇了
Fired or suspended, I'm not sure which...
解雇或停职，我不知道哪个...
Fired.
被解雇。
Anything I can help you with, just gimme a holler.
任何帮助的话，只要给我一个招呼。
Give Mildred Hayes
给Mildred Hayes
a holler.
一个招呼。
Okay.
好的。
You know me?
你认识我？
Only from the TV,
从电视上，
and the radio.
还有收音机。
How much these here 'Welcome to Missouri' rabbits go for?
这些欢迎来到密苏里州的兔子多少钱？
Seven bucks.
七块钱。
It's writ right on 'em.
上面写着呢。
Guess he ain't seven bucks now.
我想现在不值七块钱。
Why'd you coming here for?
你为什么要来这里？
What did I come in here for?
我到这里来了什么？
Well, maybe I'm a good friend of Willoughby's, how about that?
好吧，也许我是 Willoughby的好朋友，怎么样？
Are you?
你是？
Or, y'know...
或者，你知道...
maybe I was a friend of your daughter's or something.
也许我是你女儿的朋友或什么的。
How about that?
怎么样？
Were you?
你呢？
Or, uh,
或者，呃，
y'know, maybe I was the guy who fucked her while she was dying?
你知道，也许我是那个强奸她的那个人？
How about that?
又怎么样？
Were you?
是你？
No.
不是。
I would've liked to.
不过我会喜欢的。
I saw her picture in the paper there.
我在报纸上看到她的照片。
Saved by the bell, huh?
被门铃救下了，呵呵？
You owe me seven fucking dollars for the rabbit.
你他妈欠我七块的兔子。
Guess you'll have to get it off me next time I'm passing through, huh Mildred?
我想下一次我经过的时候你得自己从我身上取，呵呵，Mildred？
I guess I will.
我会的。
You don't know how glad I am to see you.
你不知道我见到你都高兴。
- What?!- That guy was trying to scare me.
- 什么？！那家伙想吓唬我
I wouldn't have said you scare easy.
没想到你这么不经吓。
I ain't the worst.
我情况还不算最坏。
What can I do for you, ma'am?
夫人，我能为你做点什么？
My husband left this for you before he shot himself in the head last night.
我丈夫昨天晚上在自己头上开枪之前要交我把这个交给你。
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Willoughby...- Are you?
- 对不起，威洛比太太- 你是？
Are you really?
你真的？
Sure I am.
当然，我是。
Surely it's the perfect ending for you, isn't it?
当然，这对你来说是完美的结局，不是吗？
It's proof
这是证明
that they've been successful, these billboards
他们已经成功了，你的这些广告牌
of yours, isn't it, a dead policeman?
成功杀死了的警察？
It's quantifiable now.
终于起作用了。
- Are you blaming this on me?- no
- 你在指责我吗？- 没有
I'm not blaming this on you. I just came to give you the letter.
我不是在责怪你。我只是来给你的信。
Now, my two little girls are out in the car,
现在，我的两个小女孩正在车外，
so I'd better not stay and chat.
所以我不能留下来聊天。
I'm not quite sure what we're going to do for the rest of the day.
我不太清楚今天剩下的时间做些什么。
It's hard to know what to do
很难知道该怎么做
the day your husband kills himself.
你丈夫杀自杀的那天。
It's hard to know what to do.
很难知道该怎么做。
Dear Mildred,
亲爱的Mildred，
Dead Man Willoughby here.
已死之人Willoughby献上 。
Firstly I wanted to apologize for dying
首先，我想为死亡道歉
without catching your daughter's killer.
没有追捕到你女儿的杀手。
It's a source of great pain to me, and it would
这对我来说是一个巨大的痛苦，
break my heart to think you thought I didn't care,
想到你以为我不在乎这个案子，会让我更伤心
cos I did care.
因为我确实在乎。
There are just some cases...
只有一些情况...
...where you never catch a break,
...你从来没有休息过，
then five years down the line
五年一直奋战在一线
some guy hears some other guy bragging about it in a bar-room
一群人听到另外群人在酒吧里吹嘘
or a jail-cell
或监狱牢房
and the whole thing is wrapped up thru sheer stupidity.
整个事情都是被愚蠢包装起来。
I hope that might be true for Angela, I really do.
我希望对Angela来说可能是真的，我真的这样做。
Second,
第二，
I gotta admit, Mildred, the billboards were a great fucking idea.
我得承认，Mildred，广告牌是一个伟大的他妈的主意。
They were like a chess move.
他们像一个象棋。
And although they had absolutely nothing to do with my dying,
虽然它们和我的死亡毫无关系，
I'm sure that everyone in town will assume that they did,
我相信城里的每个人都会认为有关系
which is why, for Willoughby's counter-move,
这就是Willoughby的反击，
I decided to pay the next month's rent on 'em.
我决定支付下个月的房租。
I thought it'd be funny,
我觉得这很有趣，
you having to defend 'em a whole 'nother month after they've stuck me in the ground.
在他们把我下葬之后那个月，你不得不为广告牌辩解。
The joke is on you, Mildred, ha ha,
在你身上开个玩笑，Mildred，哈哈，
and I hope they do not kill you.
我希望不会把你逼到绝境
So good luck with all that, and good luck with everything else too.
祝你好运，祝一切都好。
I hope and I pray that you get him.
我希望和并祈祷，你能抓到罪犯。
Well, do you want me to go down and talk to them?
那么，你想让我下去和他们交谈吗？
No I don't want you to go down and talk to them.
不，我不想让你去和他们交谈。
Somebody sending their goddam mother down to talk to the goddam police.
有人派他母亲跟警察谈话。
And say what?
说什么呢？
And say to give you your job back.
说，让你回来工作
And to get rid of the black guy.
摆脱那个黑人。
They ain't gonna listen to some guy's mother,
他们不会听一个母亲的话，
asking them to get rid of some black guy.
要求他们甩开某个黑人。
Things have moved on in The South!
南方的事情已经发生了！
Well it shouldn't've!
本不该发生的！
Will they give you some money for being laid off an' all?
他们解雇你会给你赔偿吧
I don't know what the compensation scheme is
我不知道赔偿方案是什么
for when you throw a guy out of a window, Mom.
因为当你把一个人从窗户里扔出去的时候，妈妈。
I guess I shoulda looked into that beforehand. Let me Google that!
我想我应该事先调查一下。让我 Google 下！
A couple grand, maybe?
一对夫妇，也许？
You've been there three years.
你已经在那里三年了。
Not counting the five years at the Academy.
不包括学院的五年。
Six!
六！
If you count the year you were held back.
如果你算上你留级那一年。
- Where ya going? - None of your business.
- 你去哪？ - 不关你的事。
Off to see your fancy woman?
去看你喜欢的女人？
- I don't got a fancy woman.- Yeah. I know!
- 我没有一个漂亮妞。- 是的。我知道！
- Hey, You wanna watch yourself. - Or you'll do what?
- 嘿，你想看看你自己吗。 - 你想干什么？
I'm blowin' your goddam head off.
我会打爆你的脑袋
- Oh, did you hear the news? - What news?
- 哦，你听到这个新闻了吗？ - 什么新闻？
That Dixon guy threw that Welby guy out his window this morning.
那个Dixon今天早上把Welby从窗外里扔了出来。
You're shitting me.
你在嘲笑我
Is he okay?
他没事吗？
You're shitting me!
你在嘲笑我！
Woah! Shit!
哇！我操！
Holy Shit!
马勒戈壁！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Go get the other one from the house!
去把房里的另一个灭火器拿来！
Shouldn't I call the fire department?
不应该打电话给消防部门吗？
Fuck the fire department! They probably started it!
去他妈的消防部门！ 也许就是他们放的火！
Well don't do anything stupid!
别做任何啥事！
Scumbags, scumbags, scumbags.Fucking scumbags.
笨蛋，笨蛋，笨蛋。 去他妈的笨蛋。
Shit!
我操！
Alright.
好吧。
Are you kidding me?
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Mom, What the hell are you doing?
妈妈，你到底在做什么？
Okay, Alright. Come on...
好吧，好的。来吧...
Leave it, Ma. Please It's too late.
别管了，妈妈。太晚了。
- Robbie.- Mom, leave it, please!
- 罗比。- 妈妈，离开吧！
Robbie!
罗比！
How are those hands?
你的手怎么样了？
Give us a minute.
给我们一分钟。
Can I ask you a couple questions?
我可以问你几个问题吗？
You can ask me all the questions you want if you take me down and arrest me.
如果你把逮捕了，你可以问我任何问题。
I'm not gonna arrest you, Mrs. Hayes. I got nothing to arrest you for.
我不会逮捕你，海耶斯太太。 我没理由抓捕你。
Not yet you ain't.
不，你有的。
We ain't all the enemy, y'know?
我们并不都是敌人，知道吗？
I'll crucify the motherfuckers.
我会把这些混蛋钉在十字架上。
What are you gonna do to 'em, Mildred?
Mildred，你会怎么做？
You're gonna crucify 'em, you say?
你要钉死他们，你说？
Yeah, I'm gonna crucify 'em.
是的，我要钉十字架。
Who you gonna crucify?
把谁钉十字架？
The motherfuckers?
那个混蛋？
Yeah!
是啊！
I'm gonna crucify the motherfuckers.
我要把那个混蛋钉在十字架上
Well, then those motherfuckers better watch out then,
那些混蛋可得小心了呢，
huh?
是吧？
Fucking A!
去他妈的！
What's this shit...?
这是什么鬼？
...and as sad as the spectacle of these burned out billboards might be,
...这些烧毁广告牌的景象和
in light of the death of Chief Willoughby,
Willoughby 警长的逝去一样悲伤，
this reporter for one can't help but wonder whether this finally puts an end
记者不禁在想 这一切是否终于结束了
to the strange saga of the three billboards outside of Eb...
三块广告牌的奇怪传奇...
This don't put an end to shit, you fucking retard,
这不会结束的，你他妈的傻逼，
this is just the fucking start,
这他妈的刚刚开始，
so why don't you put that on your “Good Morning Missouri fucking Wake-Up Broadcast”, bitch!
为啥不把这句放进你的“早安密苏里晨间广播”里，婊子！
I see on the TV there was a buncha fires lit outside o' town last night.
我在电视上看到，昨晚夜里镇外发生了火灾。
Buncha fires, huh?
着火了？
Out at those billboards.
在那些广告牌上。
Yeah, well, back when I was a cop I woulda been interested in who set those fires
当我还是一个警察的时候，我会对那些放火犯感兴趣
cos, technically, that's arson,
从技术上讲，这是纵火，
but as I am no longer employed by those people
但我不已经被解雇了
I don't really give a good god damn, now do I?
我确实没怎么好好干过，现在还行？
The Dixon residence.
Dixon家。
Hey Dixon.
嗨 Dixon
Hey, Sarge.
嘿，Sarge。
- You got any news? - News about what?
- 你有什么消息吗？- 关于什么的消息？
I dunno,
我不知道，
about my job and stuff?
关于我的工作？
No, no. What?
不，不。什么？
No.
没有。
Anne Willoughby just dropped in a letter
Anne Willoughby 刚刚留下了一封信
that Bill wrote you before he died.
Bill在他死前写信给你。
Oh my God! What's it say?
哦，上帝！写了些什么？
I haven't read it, Dixon, it's not my letter.
我没看过，Dixon这不是我的信。
Oh. Listen, I'll come right down...
哦。听着，我马上过去下...
I'll be there in like 15 minutes.
我15分钟内到。
Well, uh... I don't think that'd be such a great idea,
呃...我不认为这会是一个好主意，
as things stand, Jason.
杰森，从现在情况看
Uh, you've still got your keys to the station-house though, right?
呃，你还有警局的钥匙，对吗？
Yeah.
是啊。
Well, why don't you just come pick it up when everyone's gone home.
那么，不如等下班大家都走了你来拿？
I can leave it on your desk for ya.
我可以把它放在你的桌子上。
Oh. Okay.
哦。好的。
Actually, yeah,
其实，，
then when you're done you can
那么当你完事后，你可以
just leave the keys,
把钥匙留下，
save us picking 'em up later.
免得后面找你去拿。
Alright.
好的。
Jason, Willoughby here.
Jason, Willoughby呈上。
I'm dead now, sorry about that,
我现在死了，对不起，
but there's something I wanted to say to you
但是我想对你说一些话
that I never really said when I was alive.
当我还活着的时候，我可不会说这些。
I think you've got the makings of being a really good cop, Jason,
我觉得你已经是一个非常好的警察了，杰森，
and you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Because, deep down,
因为，内心深处，
you're a decent man.
你是一个体面的男人。
I know you don't think I think that, but I do, Dixon.
我知道你觉得我不这么认为，但是我是这么想的，Dixon。
I do think you're too angry, though,..
不过，我确实觉得你脾气太爆炸了。
And I know it's all since your dad died and
我知道因为你爸爸去世后
you had to go look after your Mom and all...
你必须照顾你的妈妈和一切
But as long as you hold onto so much hate
但只要你心存怨恨
then I don't think you're ever going to become...
那么我认为你永远不会成为...
What I know you wanna become...
我知道你想成为的...
A Detective.
大警探。
Cos you know what you need to become a detective.
因为你知道要成为一个警探的必须要具备的。
And I know you're gonna wince when I say this...
而且我知道当我说这个时你会退缩
But what you need to become a detective...
但是，你想要成为一个警探...
is Love.
需要的是爱。
Fuck 'em!
他妈的！
Because thru Love comes Calm,
因为只有爱会带来冷静，
and thru Calm comes Thought.
通过冷静带来思考。
And you need Thought to detect stuff sometimes, Jason.
有时候你需要思考来侦查，杰森。
It's kinda all you need.
这是你需要的。
You don't even need a gun.
你甚至不需要枪支。
And you definitely don't need Hate.
也绝对不需要恨。
Hate never solved nothing...
恨从来没有解决任何事情...
But Calm did.
但是，冷静可以。
And Thought did. Try it.
思考可以。试一下。
Try it just for a change.
尝着改变一次。
No-one'll think you're gay.
没人会认为你是同性恋。
And if they do, arrest 'em for homophobia!
如果他们这样做，以恐同罪名逮捕！
Won't they be surprised!
他们不会震惊的！
Good luck to you, Jason.
祝你好运，Jason.
You're a decent man,
你是一个体面的人，
and yeah you've had a run of bad luck...
只是运气不好。
But things are gonna change for you...
但事情有会有转变的
I can feel it.
我能感觉到。
Calm.
冷静。
So what did you see?
那么你看到了什么？
Well when we turned the corner from Spring,
那么当我们从Spring街转过来的时候，
the fire was already raging,
大火已经开始了，
and then
接着
two seconds later the cop guy just jumps out the window...
两秒钟后，警察刚跳出了窗户。
Wait.
等待。
The two of you turned the corner from Spring?
你们两个从Spring街过来的吗？
- Where were you before this? - Round at my place.
- 你之前在哪里？- 在我的地方。
You two are boyfriend and girlfriend?
你们两个是对象？
Well, it's early stages, y'know.
额，现在是早期阶段。
That right?
对吗？
We've had a couple dates.
我们有几次约会。
So you wanna go out to dinner next week?
所以你下周想去吃晚饭吗？
I'll go out to dinner with ya.
我和你一起出去吃。
But I ain't gonna fuck ya.
但我不会去操你。
Well, I ain't gonna fuck you neither.
那么，我也不会去操你。
I guess.
我猜。
Burn victim.
烧伤受害者。
He's pretty heavily sedated.
灼伤非常严重。
Hey man?
嗨，老兄？
You doing okay? Jeez,
你还好吗？Jeez，
you got burned up pretty bad.
你被烧得很严重啊
You'll be okay though.
你会没事的。
You want a glass of orange juice?
你想要一杯橙汁？
I got a straw somewhere...
我有一个吸管
Hey.
嘿。
Don't cry.
不要哭
You'll be okay.
你会没事的。
I'm sorry, Welby.
对不起，Welby.
- You know me?- I'm sorry.
- 你认识我？- 对不起。
Sorry for what?
为什么要对不起？
For throwing you out the window.
因为我把你扔出窗外。
- I'm sorry man.- I don't care.
- 我很抱歉。 我不在乎。
And stop fucking crying.
别他妈哭了。
The salt'll just fuck up your wounds.
盐会让你伤口更疼的。
I thought salt was supposed to be good for wounds.
我以为盐有利于伤口。
Well what am I, a fucking doctor?!
那我应该当医生吗？
Who is it?
你谁呀？
Oh you don't know me really.
哦，你不认识我。
Well what you want?
那你想干什么？
I come about the billboards.
关于广告牌的事儿。
What about 'em?
怎么了？
They got burned up.
他们被烧毁了。
I know that.
我知道。
I'm one of the guys who put the 'em up in the first place.
我是把他们挂起来的人，其中一位。
Jerome.
What can I do for ya, Jerome?
Jerome.我能为你做什么？
Well, y'know, when you're putting up a buncha posters like that,
嗯，你知道吗，当准备挂这种海报时，
just in case any of 'em gets screwed up or torn,
以防万一搞砸或撕裂，
they give ya a set of duplicates, y'know?
他们会给你一套备用的，你知道吗？
No, I didn't know that.
不，我不知道。
Ladder's pretty steady as it is, there, James.
James.梯子非常稳定。
Oh, that's okay. I like holding ladders.
哦，没关系。我喜欢扶着梯子。
It takes me out of myself.
能让我走会儿神
- Need a hand?- Hey.
- 需要帮忙？- 嘿。
- When'd you get out?- Hour ago.
- 你什么时候出来的？- 一个小时前。
Judge threw it out, said the arrest report weren't filled out right.
法官说逮捕报告没有正确填写，把我放了
Say, you.
所以，你。
Say, you didn't burn down the police station, did ya?
你没有纵火烧警局吧，是吗？
No. She was with me the whole night.
不，她整晚都在我身边。
- It's a long story. - Okay.
- 这是一段很长的故事。 - 好的。
- Okay. - Hey.
- 好的。 - 嘿。
Hey.
嘿。
You sure you still wanna put up the Willoughby one, him dead an' all?
你确定还想挂这些广告？Willoughby他不死了吗？
Why not? He paid for it.
为什么不？毕竟他付了钱。
True.
真的。
Look, this fucking asshole.
看，那个混蛋
Well, here we are
嗯，没想到我们能一起坐在这儿
here we are.
是没想到。
I like cheesy things.
我喜欢奶酪制品。
I'm gonna look for cheesy things.
我要找点奶酪。
Alright.
好的。
Who's that?
那是谁？
My ex-husband.
我前夫。
And his nineteen year old girlfriend.
和他十九岁的女朋友。
- You wanna leave?- No, no.
- 你想离开？- 不，不。
A deal's a deal.
一码归一码。
It was fucking wild, man,
真他妈浪
I think I was certifiably fucking insane for a while back there.
我那会儿在后面也干得贼爽。
When was this?
这是什么时候的事？
Bout nine, ten months ago.
大概九，十个月前。
- Were you on your own or what? - No, had a couple buddies with me.
- 你自己还是怎么着？ - 不，和我有几个哥们。
- Oh yeah?- Yeah.
- 是吗？- 是的。
They fuck her too?
他们也操她了？
I think they got their kicks just watching, you know.
我想他们只是看着她乱踢脚，你懂。
- Uhuh. Yeah?- Yeah.
- 额。是吗？- 是的。
Was she hot?
她性感吗？
After the gasoline kicked in she was hot.
浇上汽油才叫性感。
That's when I really wanted to fuck her even more.
那时真他妈想再干她一会儿。
I don't know if I could get that out.
我不知道能否搞定这事儿。
I ain't going down for that shit, last fucking day down there...
我不会因为那事儿蹲号的，一天也别想
He been there the whole time?
他一直在那里？
Who?
谁？
Burnt-face-Jake. Keeps fucking walking up and down.
烂脸杰克。他妈的一直走来走去。
I don't know. I don't think so.
我不知道。我没觉得啊。
- Another round.- Yeah.
- 再来一轮。- 是的。
Eight bucks.
八块钱。
Maestro.
一瓶Maestro。
Can I help you with something, man?
我可以帮你吗？
Excuse Me?
打扰一下？
You've been looking over here all fucking night,
你一整晚都他妈往这儿看，
now, unless you got something to say to me,
你有话要说吗，
why don't you take your burnt fucking face and get the fuck outta here, okay?
带着你烧焦的脸滚出去，好吗？
What are you doing?
你想干什么？
- What are you doing?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
- 你想干什么？
- 等等，等等，等等，等等...
Just trust me, okay?
相信我，好吗？
You like magic?
你喜欢魔术吗？
- Just trust me...- Just do the fucking trick.
- 相信我...- 只是个小把戏。
Okay.
好的。
What the fuck?
她妈的？
Hey.
嘿。
Hey!
嘿!
- Hey! That's enough now!- What's it to ya, fucker?
- 嘿！够了！- 算什么东西，傻逼？
- The guy's a cop man! He's a cop!- The guy's a cop man! He's a cop!
- 这人是警察！他是警察！
He ain't wearing no badge.
他没有戴警徽。
I lost my badge.
我警徽弄丢了。
I can't remember where I lost it.
我不记得在哪儿丢的。
You started this, man!
你挑起的事，家伙！
I didn't do shit to you.
我可没招惹你。
I know I started it. I scratched you up like a bitch.
我知道是我挑的事儿。像一个婊子一样挠你。
That's exactly fucking right...
你他妈没说错啊…
Gotta use the little boys' room.
我去下洗手间。
- You got something to say to me?- You got something to say to me?
- 你有话要对我说？
Doesn't shit girl have a curfew weeknights?
那小屁孩要被家长宵禁了？
No, no, in fact I was actually gonna take her to the circus later,
不，不，实际上我待会儿会带她去马戏团，
but there's no need now. Does he juggle?
但现在不必了。他是玩杂耍的吗？
Look I'm having one dinner with the guy cos he did me a favor, okay?
我和他一起吃晚餐，是因为他帮了我一个忙，好吗？
You don't have to explain yourself to me cos
你不必向我解释
you're having dinner with a midget, Mildred.
你正在和一个侏儒吃晚餐 Mildred.
- I'm not explaining myself to you. - You kinda are.
- 我不是在向你解释。 - 你在解释
Look, I didn't come over to break your balls,
我不是要来破坏你的晚宴，
you can date as many midgets as you want.
你约会多少侏儒都没问题。
No,
我没有，
I came over to say I was sorry, actually.
实际上，我过来说我很抱歉。
Sorry for what?
为什么要对不起？
I'm sorry about what happened to your billboards an' all.
广告牌着火了，我很遗憾。
Yeah well,
好的，
that's all water under the bridge now, I guess. - Good
一切顺其自然。 - 很好
I'm glad. I was pretty drunk, but it still don't excuse it.
我很高兴。我喝醉了，但这不是借口。
All this anger, man,
所有这些愤怒，
Penelope said to me the other day,
Penelope对我说，
it just begets greater anger,
只会激发更大的愤怒，
y'know?
你知道么，
And it's true.
这是真的。
Penelope said 'Begets'?
Penelope 会说“激发”？
Yeah,
是啊，
'It begets greater anger'.
“只会激发更大的愤怒”。
You take care of this little lady, okay sport?
你照顾好这位女士，好吗？
Big lady, compared to you, right?
巨人太太，和你比起来算是？
- You alright? - I think I'd like to go home now.
- 你还好吗？ 我想我现在想回家
Don't gimme any shit, James? We can do this another time, alright?
Jame，别介意？我们可以再来一次，好吗？
Why would I wanna do this another time? You've been
为什么我会再来一次呢？ 你一直
embarrassed to be here ever since we arrived.
一直很尴尬，自从我们到达之后
- Oh for Christ's sakes,
- 哦，上帝，
I didn't force you to come on this date,
我没有强迫你来赴约，
alright? You forced me.
是吗？你强迫我了
Forced you?
强迫你？
I asked you on a date.
我只是请你赴约
Wow! Well, y'know,
哇！那么，你知道，
I know
我知道
I ain't much of a catch, okay?
我不配和你在一起，好吧？
I know I'm a dwarf who sells used cars and has a drinking problem, I know that.
我知道我是一个卖二手车的侏儒，而且有饮酒问题， 我知道。
But who the hell are you, man?
但是你她妈是谁？
You're that Billboard Lady who never ever smiles,
你是从来不笑的的广告牌女士，
who never has a good word to say about anybody,
对于任何人，从来没有一句好话可说，
and who, in the evening times, SETS FUCKING FIRE TO POLICE STATIONS!
大半夜，在警察局防火！
And I'M the one who's not a catch?!
而我，不配和你约会？！
Hey!
嘿!
Y'know I didn't have to come and hold your ladder!
你知道，我本不必来帮你扶梯子的！
Now don't make a scene.
现在别大吵大闹。
Did you really tell him “Anger begets greater anger”?
真是你诉他“愤怒会激发更大的愤怒吗”？
Oh! Yes!
哦!是!
I did! I didn't make it up myself though.
是我说的！不过不是我写的。
I can't claim that! No, I read it on a bookmark.
不是我原创的！，我在书签上读到的。
Which was in a book I was reading.
我正在读一本书。
About polio.
关于小儿麻痹症
Polo. No, which is the one with the horses? Polio?
马球。不，是那本马匹？脊髓灰质炎？
- Polo?- Polo.
- 马球？- 马球。
Be nice to her, Charlie.
对她好点， Charlie.
You got that?
听到没？
Jason!
Just leave me, don't look at me, Momma.
别管我，别看我，妈妈。
You..
你..
No! Do not!
别！不要！
Don't.
别。
Open up this door!
打开门！
Please, Jason.
求你了，Jason.
I'll help you.
我来帮你。
Please, open the door.
求你开开门。
Please.
求你了。
求求你。
Please, open the door.
求你，开开们。
Open up!
打开！
Jason!
I'm alright, Momma.
妈妈，我没事
It's all gonna be alright.
一切都会好起来的。
I don't wanna get your hopes up, alright, but there's a guy,
我不想让你抱太大期望，但有一个人，
and I think he might be the guy.
我想他可能就是那个嫌疑犯。
I got his DNA.
我得到了他的DNA。
I got a lot of it, actually.
实际上，我拿了很多。
They're making the checks as we speak. - He's in jail?
他们正在做检查。他在监狱里？
No, but he ain't gonna be hard to find.
不，但抓到他并不难。
Why do you think he's the guy?
你为什么认定他是那个人？
I heard him talking about something that he did to a girl
我听到他在谈论他对一个女孩所做的事
in the middle of last year.
在去年年中。
I couldn't hear all of it, but
我没有听全，但是
it sounded a lot likewhat happened to Angela.
听起来很像Angela的案子
Then he beat the crap outta me.
然后他给我胖揍了一顿。
But cos of that
但是，因为这个
I got a bunch of his DNA.
我得到了一堆他的DNA。
So I wanted
所以我想要
to let you know sooner rather than later. I didn't want you to give up hope, y'know?
让你早日知道。我不想让你放弃希望，你知道吗？
I've been trying not to.
我一直在努力。
Well, all you can do is try, as my Momma says.
我所能做的就是不断尝试，就像妈妈说的那样。
Not so much about hope as about...
没有那么多关于希望...
well, I didn't used to be
好吧，我以前
very good at English at school,
在学校英语不是很好，
so it was more “All you can do is try...
你所能做的就是尝试...
to not be so crap at English.”
说英语时不要这么多废话。“
Cos you need English, really, if you wanna be a cop.
如果你想成为一名警察，你真的需要英语
If you wanna be anything.
如果你想成事儿。
Really.
真。
Unless you live in Mexico or something.
除非你住在墨西哥之类的。
But who wants that?
但谁想去那儿？
Hey, Dixon.
嘿，Dixon.
Thank you!
谢谢！
You did good, Jason.
你做得很好，Jason。
You did real good.
你真的很好。
But he wasn't the guy.
但他不是那个人。
What?
什么？
There was no match to the DNA,
DNA没有匹配，
no matches to any other crimes of this nature,
没有匹配到任何犯罪记录，
to any crimes at all, in fact.
没任何犯罪记录。
And his record is clean.
他的纪录很干净
Maybe he was just bragging.
也许他只是在吹牛。
He wasn't just bragging.
他不是吹牛。
Well, that's as may be. But at the time of Angela's death
这有可能的。但在Angela去世的时候
he wasn't even in the country.
他甚至不在州内。
Where was he?
他在哪里？
But I've seen his records of entry and exit to the States,
但是我看过他的入境和出境记录，
and I've spoken to his Commanding Officer.
我已经和他的指挥官聊过了。
He wasn't in the country, Dixon.
他不在本州，Dixon.
He ain't our guy.
他不是我们的人。
No, he ..
不，他..
He might not be our guy, but he still done something shitty. I know he did.
他也许不是我们的人，但他肯定干了坏事。我知道他做了。
Not in Missouri he didn't.
在密苏里州没有，他没有。
Where was he?
他当时在哪里？
That's classified information.	*
这是机密信息。
Come on, man.
得了吧，伙计。
If the guy's got a Commanding Officer,
如果这个人有一个指挥官，
and if the guy got back to the country nine months ago,
如果这个人在九个月前回了密苏里州，
and if the country where he was is classified,
如果他所在的州是机密，
which country do you think he was in?
你认为他在哪个州？
Hey, you know ..
嘿，你知道..
I'll give you a clue.
我会给你一个线索。
It was sandy.
是沙质的。
That doesn't really narrow it down.
这并没有真正缩小范围。
All you need to know is,
所有你需要知道的是，
he didn't do nothing to Angela Hayes.
他真和Angela Hayes案子无关。
So we're gonna keep looking.
所以我们还得继续找。
Alright?
好的？
I found my badge after all.
我找到了我的警徽。
Hello?
你好？
It's Dixon.
我是Dixon。
Tell me.
说吧。
He wasn't the guy.
他不是那个人。
Mildred?
Are you're sure?
你确定吗？
He, um, he wasn't even in the country when it happened.
他呢，他当时不在本州。
So, whatever he did,
所以，无论他做了什么，
he didn't do it round here.
他没有在这里做。
I'm sorry I got your hopes up.
对不起，我吊起了你的希望。
It's alright.
没关系。
At least I had a day of hoping. Which is more than I've had for a while.
至少我有了一天的希望，已经好一阵没这样了。
I'd better go.
我最好还是出发。
There was
有
there was one thing I was thinking.
有一件事我在想。
What's that?
那是什么？
Well... I know he isn't your rapist.
那么...我知道他不是这起案子的强奸犯。
He is a rapist, though.
不过，他是一个强奸犯。
I'm sure of that.
我确信这一点。
What are you saying to me?
你在跟我说什么
I got his license plate.
我拿到了他的车牌号。
I know where he lives.
我知道他住在哪里
Where's he live?
他住在哪里？
Lives in Idaho.
住在爱达荷州。
That's funny.
这是有趣的。
I'm driving to Idaho in the morning.
我早上开车去爱达荷。
Want some company?
想要搭档吗？
Sure.
当然。
Hey, Dixon.
嘿，Dixon.
Yeah?
怎么？
I need to tell you something.
我要告诉你一件事。
It was me who burned
down the police station.
是我烧毁了派出所。
Well, who the Hell else would it have been?
好吧，除了你还会有谁呢？
Dixon?
Yep?
怎么？
You sure about this?
你确定要这么干吗？
About killing this guy?
关于杀了这个人？
Not really.
不是很确定哈。
You?
你呢？
Not really.
也不太确定。
I guess we can decide along the way.
我想我们可以在路上再做决定。
翻译：三十九度二
最新影视资源 请关注公众号  三十九度二